SEBASTIAN KOZICKI

open to remote work or relocation

9 years 12+ 500+ of design programs visual experience &apps used projects



LINKEDIN

BEHANCE

CONTACT ME

E-mail:

sebastian.kozicki1@gmail.com

Mob.

+48.601.50.32.63

ABOUT ME IN A NUTSHELL

UI/Web designer with the ability to empathize with people and create solutions that are simple, aesthetically pleasing and in line with client expectations. An experienced creative that has helped companies from over 8 industries meet clients' and employers' goals.

DESIGN TOOLS

Figma
Adobe Xd CC
PhotoShop CC
Illustrator CC
InDesign CC
VS Code
WordPress
Miro / Notion / Trello ...and more

AI SUPPORTING TOOLS

Relume Uizard Autodesigner Leonardo Ai Chat GPT Bard / Open Ai / Perplexity

DESIGN SKILLS

typography / color layout composition wireframing / prototyping responsive web / app design HTML5 / CSS3

SOFT SKILLS

fast learner looking globally communication goal orientation team player ...and more

LANGUAGE

english: professional comunicative polish: native french: pre-beginner

SOME OF MY DESIGN ACTIVITIES

ux/ui hub

Vitamin K, 2024 my role: **UI designer**

Cooperating with Vitamin K, providing ideas and design for the application and web, UX writing, and helping with manage data in Airtable.

portfolio site

2023

my role: web designer / front-end developer

My portfolio website - I designed and coded the website myself using VS Code and the GitHub repository.

web application

HomeFix Hub- concept, 2024 my role: **UI designer**

A social platform for offering and seeking help in the field of private renovation of houses and apartments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

visual designer & creative consultant

05.2015 - present, 3C, Poland & remote

Collaborating with diverse clients, assisting them in meeting their business needs while creating captivating and impactful visual experiences. Discuss, understand, conduct research, and develop projects considering the budget, use cases, and client's goals.

Clients receive valued market insight and high-quality materials following the agreed brief improves the clients' visibility and public appearance.

Working with cross-functional teams from different countries (Poland, Eastern Europe, and Egypt) and **collaborated with developers** from the United States for private projects.

team leader / printing technologist

11.2016 - 10.2018 & 11.2019-04.2021, bySolara, Poland

Coordinating a printing department of 3 people.

Managed the flow of materials along with the team, conducted desktop publishing projects review, acted as a connector between the sales and production departments and worked with the unique needs of clients and subcontractors.

Printed materials and ensured almost 100 percent quality and on-time delivery to customers.

print & copy editing coordinator

06.2019 - 08.2019, Avon, Poland

Delivering layouts for Avon catalog every three weeks in 5 languages.

Conducting desktop publishing and communicating with graphics designers to make recommendations and resolve issues.

Avon catalog was published on time every three weeks for 5 countries, ensuring product sales continued.

EDUCATION